40days40nightsprogram.com 2015-08-11

# Max Hair Growth

We don't share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.  
We don't store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of one of our services.  
In our blogging products and forums, we aim to make it as simple as possible for you to control what's visible to the public, seen by search engines, kept private, and permanently deleted.  
Tatooine Global Ltd. operates several websites. It is Tatooine Global Ltd. 's policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites. 

**Website Visitors**

Like most website operators, Tatooine Global Ltd. collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. Tatooine Global Ltd. 's purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how Tatooine Global Ltd. 's visitors use its website. From time to time, Tatooine Global Ltd. may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.  
Tatooine Global Ltd. also collects potentially personally identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. Tatooine Global Ltd. does not use such information to identify its visitors, however, and does not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information, as described below. 

**Gathering of Personally Identifying Information**

Tatooine Global Ltd. is the sole owner of information collected on this site to purchase products and services from 40days40nightsprogram.com. We will not sell, share or rent this information to any outside parties, except as outlined in this policy. We collect information from our customers to process orders and better serve you with pertinent information, such as order confirmations and order status updates. Information collected includes your name, shipping address, billing address, telephone numbers, email address and payment information, such as your credit/debit card number. 

**Choice/Opt-out**

If you receive a marketing email from Tatooine Global Ltd. and would prefer to not receive these types of messages, click the "unsubscribe" link in the email footer to remove your name from our list 

**Children**

Tatooine Global Ltd. does not sell products for purchase by children. If you are under the age of 18, you may only use 40days40nightsprogram.com in the presence of a consenting parent or guardian. We will not knowingly or intentionally collect personal information via the Internet from children under the age of 18. Tatooine Global Ltd. is committed to protecting the welfare and privacy of children. 

**Aggregated Statistics**

Tatooine Global Ltd. may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. Tatooine Global Ltd. may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, Tatooine Global Ltd. does not disclose personally identifying information other than as described below. 

**Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information**

Tatooine Global Ltd. discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on Tatooine Global Ltd. 's behalf or to provide services available at Tatooine Global Ltd. 's websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using Tatooine Global Ltd. 's websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. Tatooine Global Ltd. will not rent or sell potentially personally identifying and personally identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, Tatooine Global Ltd. discloses potentially personally identifying and personally identifying information only when required to do so by law, or when Tatooine Global Ltd. believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of Tatooine Global Ltd. , third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an Tatooine Global Ltd. website and have supplied your email address, Tatooine Global Ltd. may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what's going on with Tatooine Global Ltd. and our products. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. Tatooine Global Ltd. takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally identifying and personally identifying information. 

**14-Day Trial**

Your package will contain one bottle of Max Hair Growth™! As part of the 14-day trial and Lifestyle Auto-Ship Program, you will be charged $3.98 today for shipping and handling of Max Hair Growth. If the order is not cancelled before the end of the trial period, on the 15th day, you will be charged $94.99 for the full retail price of the product. 

**Lifestyle Auto-Ship Program**

As part of the Lifestyles Autoship Program, starting in 45 days from the date of your original order you will receive 1 bottle per month for a charge of $89.99 (+ $4.95 s&h) reoccurring monthly until cancelled. 

If for any reason, you are not satisfied, and you are within the 14 days of date of order, simply call (844) 275-7518 Monday-Friday 8am-5pm PST or email [info@40days40nightsprogram.com](mailto:info@40days40nightsprogram.com) to cancel your trial and subsequent shipments and you will have no further obligation. Also, remember that at any time you can modify your Lifestyles Auto-Ship Program shipments or if you are not completely satisfied, just call us to cancel. 

**Cookies**

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor's computer, and that the visitor's browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Tatooine Global Ltd. uses cookies to help Tatooine Global Ltd. identify and track visitors, their usage of Tatooine Global Ltd. website, and their website access preferences. Tatooine Global Ltd. visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using Tatooine Global Ltd. 's websites, with the drawback that certain features of Tatooine Global Ltd. 's websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies. 

**Ads**

Advertising partners, who may set cookies, may deliver ads appearing on any of our websites to users. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by Tatooine Global Ltd. and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. 

**Privacy Policy Changes**

Although most changes are likely to be minor, Tatooine Global Ltd. may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in Tatooine Global Ltd. 's sole discretion. Tatooine Global Ltd. encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change. 

**Last updated: 1/2015**

If you have questions about accessing or correcting your personal data please contact our customer service department using the contact information on this website.
